Hello?
Yes.
It's my first time, but is it okay now?
Yes, that's right.
Is it okay?
Well, from now on,
Please in 60 minutes.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
The address is
Please in 60 minutes.
Yes.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
I'm Reiko, who just came from the president's massage.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
It's very beautiful.
Please come in.
Yes, excuse me.
It's hard to pack.
Is it comfortable?
Yes.
You seem to be angry.
That's right.
Do you often get a massage?
Not at all.
It's hard to pack so much.
Really?
Yes.
Wow.
Are you okay?
Yes.
That's good.
Is this job long?
Well,
It's been about two or three years.
I'm getting used to it.
Yes.
It's good.
It's beautiful.
The massage is good.
It's the best.
Not at all.
Thank you very much.
Yes.
Could you turn around a little?
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
It's okay.
What's wrong?
What?
Something.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Reiko's massage is a little
It's very comfortable.
I'm sorry.
What?
It's okay.
It's because it feels good.
Yes.
If it was so good, everyone would have gotten angry.
What?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
If you have any, please send me a message.
I'm sorry.
What?
That's a little ...
Is the center of the body okay?
Here?
It's so stiff.
What?
The center of the body is the most slender.
That's right.
But here ...
Please.
I can't let go of your hand.
Are you not satisfied?
That's not true.
Maybe you haven't slept at all with your husband.
I'm really in trouble.
Do you have a rope?
What is a rope?
What?
This is a free service.
I don't have such a thing.
You don't have it?
Yes.
Then just a little.
What?
You don't have to move, so please use it a little.
Please.
It's tight and dangerous.
What?
Please.
You don't have to move your hands, I'll move them.
What?
No.
You look very happy.
What should I do?
What?
No.
You don't feel good just touching it?
That's not true.
Really?
Can you lick it a little?
What?
Just a little.
Just a little?
Is that okay?
You are very kind.
Thank you.
You said you were amazing.
Your tinkle is amazing.
Excuse me.
Do you like tinkle?
No.
I have to do it again.
What?
It's okay.
What do you mean?
I'll take it out from here.
Let me see.
Your stomach is very hard.
It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing?
Why are you embarrassed?
Why is your tinkle so hard?
Your tinkle is amazing.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
I'm scared.
I can see everything.
No.
Please stick out more.
Excuse me.
1, 2, 3.
I'll give you water.
Are you okay?
It's hot.
Amazing.
Does it feel good?
No.
Do you want to do something?
What do you think it is?
No.
What?
Don't you want to spill this big blood?
I can't do that.
You don't want to do it with your husband, do you?
No.
But...
But what?
You don't want to do it with your husband, do you?
You don't want to be exposed, do you?
Open your legs.
It's going to go in.
It's hot.
It's okay.
Please be quiet.
It's hot.
It's going to go in.
Please be quiet.
What do you want to do?
Your neck is chipped.
It's the limit of endurance.
Can I put it out?
No, you can't.
I can't put it out?
Then I'll put it out in your mouth.
It's going to go in.
Okay.
Show me your mouth.
I'm sorry, but please keep it a secret.
I won't tell you.
Are you satisfied with the massage?
Of course.
Thank you.
I'll be waiting for your next assignment.
It's going to go in.
Hello?
Yes.
I'd like to have a massage.
I see.
I'd like you to come right away.
Yes.
If you're available.
Yes, that's right.
I see.
Hello.
I'm Shiori from Hitozuma.
Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Hello.
Does your back hurt a lot?
Yes.
I often sit down.
Okay.
My back hurts a lot.
It's hard.
I see.
Is your strength okay?
Yes, it's okay.
Okay.
I heard that you're a newcomer to the shop.
Yes.
You're good.
I'm a newcomer to the shop, but I used to work at another shop.
I see.
Yes.
You're really good.
Please tell me if it hurts.
Okay.
Your back is just right.
Thank you.
Do you do desk work?
No, I'm not doing desk work.
I'm doing something like a free lighter.
I see.
You're working on a computer.
Yes.
I'm working on a computer.
You're working on your neck and shoulders.
Yes.
I'm glad you came to my shop.
I'm going to...
Yes.
If you don't want to answer, you don't have to answer.
Okay.
I had a question about your shop.
Are you getting married?
Yes.
I see.
I envy you.
No.
There are so many beautiful people at home every day.
Do you give your husband a massage?
Not really.
I see.
He gets tired.
Your husband?
Yes.
I see.
I'd like to have your husband's baby.
Are you married?
No, I'm not.
You're still young.
I'm old enough to get married.
But I don't have a boyfriend.
I see.
I don't have a boyfriend.
You don't have a boyfriend.
I see.
I'm stuck at home all the time.
I don't have a chance to meet him.
I have a lonely life.
I see.
I think it's time.
I'd like to have blue hair.
Okay.
Your legs are swollen.
I see.
Your thighs are swollen, too.
Really?
Yes.
I don't know much about myself.
I see.
I have to ask a specialist to check my legs.
Your legs are swollen.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I have a lint roller.
It hurts.
I see.
I'll press it lightly.
It's okay.
I don't need a massage.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's been a long time since I've had a massage.
It feels good.
It's good for my blood circulation.
I've had a stomachache.
It's common.
Don't worry about it.
Is it common?
I have a lot of male customers.
You have a stomachache?
Yes.
I see.
Are you used to it?
No.
That's right.
I encounter such a situation.
I see.
Shiori.
Yes.
Do you have a lint roller?
What's a lint roller?
You'll understand when I say lint roller.
It's useless.
I don't have such a service.
I'm sorry.
But you said you had a stomachache.
I can't do anything more just by having a stomachache.
I see.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
You shouldn't do that.
It's okay.
I see.
It's easy to do.
I have to move.
It's okay.
I'll give you a massage.
I'll do it on time.
That's right.
It's the first time I've had a massage in front of me.
A massage?
No.
You're doing a terrible job.
I'm sorry.
Please stop.
I can't concentrate on the massage.
It's okay, right?
No, it's not okay.
It's okay.
Please stop.
Shiori, you can hold my hand.
What?
I'll move it.
No, no, no.
This part is the hardest.
What?
I'm in trouble.
You said you should stand up.
No, no.
I didn't say that.
You said you should stand up to massage your feet.
That's not what I meant.
No.
That's why I said you should stand up.
Let me stand up.
No.
I don't want to be scolded by the store anymore.
No, that's why you should run away.
What?
It's okay.
It's so big.
I'll move it.
It feels good.
You're good at massaging.
Yes.
You're good at this too.
Is it okay now?
No, no, no.
You have to relax properly.
You have to relax.
I don't know how to relax.
Relaxing is like a massage.
You know what I mean?
Please stop.
I'm trying to convey the image of gently massaging.
It feels good.
I'm having a hard time these days.
No, no, no.
You're good at this.
Yes.
You're massaging gently.
Please don't tell the store.
Just a little.
It'll be over soon.
It's soft.
Is that so?
I want you to do it clearly.
What?
The real thing?
I want you to do it clearly.
What do you mean by the real thing?
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect you to do that.
I misheard you.
It's the real thing, isn't it?
I didn't say that.
I'm fine with this much.
Isn't it?
Your nipples are here, aren't they?
No, they're not.
Please tell me where they are.
Where are the nipples?
I don't know where the nipples are.
Can I look for them?
It's soft.
Is your husband biting you?
I don't get along with my husband.
Why?
It's a pity.
Your nipples are very long.
Are they long?
No, they're not.
Really?
They look long to me.
Your nipples are so long that you can see them.
Look at your nipples.
They're wet, aren't they?
Aren't they?
No, they're not.
They're not wet?
I wonder what the nipples are.
They're soaked.
Your nipples are so long.
No, they're not.
They're wet.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Do you do this every day?
Do you have nipples other than your husband?
No, I don't.
Your nipples are sticking out.
Long time no see.
Yes.
It's been a long time.
Your nipples are wet, aren't they?
No, they're not.
Really?
Your pants are wet.
Your pants are wet, but your nipples are sticking out.
Your nipples are sticking out.
You're making a great sound.
You like being patted.
What's the matter?
I'm scared.
You're scared?
What's the matter?
Don't look at me.
It feels good.
Your finger went in.
You're a baby.
Your nipples are small.
It feels good.
Don't look at me.
How far can you go?
Just your mouth.
It feels really good.
You're really good at licking.
Really?
Yeah.
Can I do it?
No.
It's okay.
We've come this far.
We're going to keep it a secret.
You're sleeping well.
Ah.
I haven't been with my husband lately.
I'm not feeling well.
Ah.
It feels good.
You have a sexy body.
When did you get it?
It's been a year.
Really?
You're so young.
I'd do it every day.
Ah.
Stretch out your legs.
Shibu,
bend down yourself.
Ah.
It's been a while.
How do you feel?
Ah.
That's not good.
No?
Not inside.
If it's not inside, can I go anywhere?
Yes.
This is how I feel.
I'm sorry.
I told you not to go inside.
I don't want to mess up anything else.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Please don't clean up.
Please don't do this again.
Of course.
Did you feel good?
I'm waiting for your order again.
I'm coming.
What?
The chief massage.
The real person will heal you.
I'll make an appointment.
Hello?
Yes.
I'd like to call you home right now.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Really?
Can you close this?
Yes.
I'm looking at your website.
Sarah, are you okay?
Yes.
Yes, please.
Hello.
I'm Sarah from Hitotsuma Massage.
Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
Thank you.
How is your strength?
It's perfect.
Is it perfect?
Yes.
You're strong.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm strong.
Do you have a sense of self-awareness?
Yes.
It's very hard.
Is it very hard?
Is it okay?
Yes, please.
It's very hard.
Isn't it painful when it's so hard?
It happens sometimes.
That's right.
This shop is called Hitotsuma Massage.
Yes.
Are you really from Hitotsuma?
Really?
Of course I'm from Hitotsuma.
All the children in the shop are married.
That's right.
It says Hitotsuma.
I'm a little worried.
That's right.
Please put a little more pressure on your back.
Okay.
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
Is it okay?
Your body is getting hot.
Really?
It's a sign of lymph flow.
Is that so?
Yes.
How is it?
Is it better than before?
That's right.
Does it hurt?
Does it feel good?
Excuse me.
This muscle.
How is it?
It's good, isn't it?
It's about time to get arm muscles.
Arm muscles?
Yes.
Life alone is amazing.
What are you talking about?
Your feet.
Please relax.
Your feet are cold.
Why are your feet so cold?
It was cold.
It's cold.
Only the tip of your feet is very cold.
Please relax.
Does it feel good?
It feels really good.
You're putting too much pressure on your back.
Please relax when you get a massage.
Okay.
Don't put too much pressure on your back.
This is the calf muscle.
Okay.
I'm going to massage it.
There is lymph.
If you get stuck here, your whole body's blood will freeze.
That's why your feet are so cold.
I see.
Excuse me.
What?
Well...
What's wrong?
What?
Well...
I'm sorry.
Please lift your buttocks.
Your pants are tight.
Excuse me.
Hey.
You're young.
You'll get better.
Well...
Yes?
Isn't there a lab here?
What's a lab?
Well...
It's a free service.
Free?
Yes.
Well...
It's not here.
It's just a massage shop.
Wait a minute.
No, no.
Just a little massage.
What?
Well...
If you get angry at the shop,
No, it's not like that.
Please calm down.
I'm calm.
You're calm?
Well...
There's no such thing at the shop.
No, no.
Just a little massage is fine.
What?
Just a little more.
It's hot.
My toes are cold.
It's so hot in here.
Well...
Yes?
Just a little more.
Well...
If you just touch it...
I'll massage your back.
Like this?
Well...
Is it okay?
Did you feel better when you were being massaged?
Yes.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
I'm surprised because it's big.
Can I get a massage in person?
What?
Well...
What should I do if it's hot?
Does it feel good?
Yes.
Which one feels better?
This one feels better.
This one feels better?
It's healthy.
It's getting hot.
It's getting so big that I can't hold it in one hand.
Yes?
I can't stand it either.
Can I do it?
What?
What is it?
I want to do more.
You want to do more?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
You don't have to tell me.
Well...
It's okay.
Wait a minute.
Can I do it with my hands?
No, I can't do it with just my hands.
Well...
Please.
It's going to be on my neck.
It's okay.
I'm begging you.
Please.
I don't like you and Sarah here.
Well, that's right.
You'll never find out.
Well...
Let's calm down.
I'm calm.
Please.
Wait a minute.
Can you really not tell me?
I don't want to.
My hands are so dirty.
Sarah's body is very warm.
If I do this, I'll get hot.
Oh, no.
I'm going to give you a massage.
Don't look at me.
Sarah's body is very dirty.
I'm not sensitive.
Wait a minute.
Are you really not satisfied?
Why?
You're getting more and more sexy.
I'm going to do all kinds of nice things.
Yes, you're going to do it.
I'm not going to do it.
I don't know...
Why do you have so many tea bags at work?
It's not like that. I only have tea bags.
I can't do this at work.
I can't do this.
I can't stand it anymore.
I can see your buttocks and buttocks.
It hurts.
It's messy.
Try moving it yourself.
It's so thick.
I'm begging you.
Does it feel good?
I'll try to make you feel better.
It's okay now.
It was just the first round.
It's all round.
It's making a lot of noise.
Is it that messy?
It's very messy.
It hurts.
Does it feel good?
It's harder than it looks.
Is it too big?
Please don't tell the store.
Of course.
It hurts.
How does it feel compared to your husband?
It's not like that.
Your husband is bigger and harder.
Look at my face.
Does it feel good?
Please don't tell the store.
Do you like being pinched?
It feels good.
It's messy.
How does it feel?
It's harder.
Does it feel good?
I can't stand it anymore.
It's not like that.
Please lie down.
You understand, don't you?
It's not like that.
It's okay.
Is it okay with your hands and mouth?
It hurts.
It's okay.
Please don't tell the store.
It's going to be okay.
It's not like that.
Does it feel good?
It's okay.
It feels good.
I'm fine.
You don't like being fine?
It's amazing.
It's crazy.
It's going to be okay.
Achi-kun...
I'm sorry, I made you cry so much.
You're such a good girl.
I'm sorry.
My butt feels so good.
No matter how hard I try...
Do you want to do more?
Please.
Yes.
My butt feels so good.
It feels so good.
Please look over here.
My butt feels so good.
It feels so good.
Sarah-san...
Can I put you inside?
No, you can't.
You can't put me inside.
Please don't make fun of me.
Please put Sarah-san's beautiful face inside.
Was the massage good?
Please don't make fun of me.
I'm sorry.
I'll be waiting for your next call.
This person is...
Hello?
Yes.
I called you from the home page.
Well...
The course...
It's 60 minutes.
Yes, that's right.
It's 30 minutes later.
I understand.
Yes, I understand.
Yes, thank you.
Yes.
Are you sure it's Kayama-sama?
I'm Chigusa from Chichou Massage.
Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
Thank you.
You're really good.
Really?
Is it okay if I use force?
Yes, it's okay.
If it hurts, please tell me.
Yes.
You're really tough.
Oh, really?
Do you use a bathrobe?
Well...
You're alone.
If I don't give you blood, you'll get hurt.
Oh, I see.
You're alone.
You're looking for a bath in the shower.
That's right.
It feels good.
You're used to it.
No, no, no.
Is it long?
Well...
It's not that long.
So...
Maybe there's something I want to say.
You're really good.
Really?
I'm glad.
Oh, that's great.
It's okay.
Oh, it's stretching.
It's stretching?
Yes.
Well...
That's right.
This side is hard.
Well, it's good.
That's right.
Well...
Yes.
Please turn to the side.
Oh, to the side.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's a little cold, so I'll put it on.
Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry.
There you go.
Please open your eyes.
Yes.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Does it hurt?
Is it okay?
Oh, it's okay.
Look at the name of the store.
It's written on the name of the store.
Oh, it's rare.
It's really good.
Is that so?
Yes.
How long have you been married?
What?
Well...
It's been about 15 years.
Oh, I see.
Are you close to your husband?
Well...
The inside is good.
Oh, I see.
It's very attractive.
No, no, no.
Thank you very much.
Oh, this side is also pasted.
Oh, I see.
Oh, it feels good there.
Here?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
It hurts, doesn't it?
Does it hurt?
Is it okay?
Oh, it's okay.
Oh, it's coming slowly.
It's coming slowly.
Is it okay?
Yes.
I'll press it.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Are there any children?
Oh, there is.
Only one.
Yes.
I'm glad.
What?
It's a little...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing something bad.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
I didn't think the cat would be able to get surgery with the panties.
Oh, I think it's best to accept it with a comfortable costume.
It's okay to press it.
Is it around here?
Yes.
Can I ask you to put it on?
Recently, my hip joints have been hurting.
Oh, I understand.
Have you ever been told that it's shallow?
What?
Is it shallow?
Yes, it's said to be the same as shallow.
Is it?
Yes.
Oh, it's wrinkled around here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's cute.
Is it here?
It's wrinkled.
Oh, really?
Then, around here.
Oh, wait a minute.
What happened?
I'm sorry.
Is your face okay?
It's okay.
Is it painful?
Yes, it's okay.
What happened?
Oh, no.
Oh, my buttocks.
What's wrong with your buttocks?
It's like puk puk.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Oh, great.
You're fine.
This shop doesn't have an option service.
Oh, is it an option?
Yes.
No, we don't do that kind of service.
You know, there's an oil massage at any shop.
Oh, really?
I don't think there's anything like that.
I don't think so.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You're a customer.
It's warm.
I didn't do anything.
It's like you're breathing.
Then, shall we massage somewhere else?
Oh, yes.
I'd like you to massage somewhere else.
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Oh, my buttocks.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
I'd like to massage your buttocks.
Can I have a massage for your buttocks?
My buttocks?
Yes.
Like this?
I see.
I know you don't have an option.
Yes.
Don't you have a back-up?
What's a back-up?
You know that, don't you?
No.
Because you're a tiger.
No, I don't do it.
You don't do it, do you?
I don't do it.
I'm in trouble.
It's amazing.
If you get hit by a stick...
Oh, come on.
Please promise me you won't tell anyone.
Of course.
I won't tell anyone.
I'll open the door for you.
Okay.
Please don't tell anyone.
Of course.
I won't tell anyone.
If you get hit by a stick...
Don't talk to anyone.
No, no.
I'm in trouble.
Just a little bit.
No, no.
What?
I'm in trouble.
Please keep it a secret.
Okay.
Like this?
It feels good.
Yes.
This feels the best when I massage you.
I see.
You lick me like crazy.
What have you been up to lately?
I'm having a lesson with my husband.
I see.
It's a good time, isn't it?
It's a lesson, isn't it?
That's right, but...
It's not good, is it?
No, it's not.
Why not?
Just my hands.
You said just your hands, but you're talking.
All you have to do is put it in.
Put it in?
Yes.
I won't let go of it.
Please show it to me.
Wait a minute.
That's...
If you're not doing it with your husband,
you're hiding, aren't you?
Your pants are wet, aren't they?
What?
You're not doing it with your husband, are you?
Here.
Put it on your butt.
It's not good.
Please don't cry.
Does it feel good?
Yes.
It feels good.
It's all over your butt.
One finger isn't enough, is it?
That's a lie.
That's not good.
It feels good.
It's raining.
It hurts.
That's not good.
It feels good.
It hurts a little, doesn't it?
That's not good.
It's not good.
Be honest.
But...
It's not good to put it in.
It's not good.
It's crumpled.
Just a little.
Compared to your husband.
Please don't tell the store.
It's not good to put it in.
It's good to put it in.
It's hot.
It's not good.
It's not good to put it in.
How is it?
You're in a bad mood.
You're crying all the time.
Which do you want?
I'm embarrassed.
Tell me.
Which do you want?
I'm embarrassed.
It feels good, doesn't it?
It hurts.
It really hurts.
Hold your feet.
Show me your ankle.
It hurts.
Don't spread your legs.
It doesn't matter.
It's a different angle.
Are you going again?
I'm going.
It's going.
It's a different angle.
Oh my god!
He is shaking hands and legs.
It's so far.
This is no good.
I have a cramp.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Oh my god.
It feels so good...
You know how easy it is to be a dork, right?
It really feels good, right?
You had a lot of hahahaha gel.
Can I get it out?
Why?
It's cold...
I'm hungry...
That's ok, if you have sex with a man...
But I'm...
I'm sorry...
You can't do anything about it?
I can't do anything about it.
You can't do anything about it, right?
It feels so good.
It feels good.
I'm about to die.
Clean it up.
It's all crumpled up.
Are you satisfied with the massage?
Of course.
Please don't tell the owner that it's crumpled up.
I won't tell him.
I'll be waiting for another massage.